We are rocking out here with Shantae Wayans, our headliner of the week.
And we've been talking about our favorite cities.
What's been a good party city for y'all?
I would say Dallas.
I go with Orlando.
Really Miami.
I say Miami.
And that's because I know someone who threw clubs there.
So when I go to Miami, it's a different experience than I had in Miami.
Yeah.
I've left my party days behind, but I'm going to still have to say New York.
Because my days in New York, I mean, legendary.
I have a whole series that I want to write about my days in New York.
You know, I mean, it was just, it was a time.
You know what I would say.
It was a time.
I say D.C.
D.C.?
Yeah.
I grew up in Maryland.
So that's where, when I was partying like that, I was going home.
Now I've heard though that current day D.C., it ain't that.
No, I don't think so.
You know what?
Atlanta.
Atlanta in the 2000s during the crunk era.
Let me tell y'all.
Not the crunk era.
Yes.
That is Atlanta.
No, not the crunk era.
The crunk.
Oh.
Crunk, crunk, crunk.
Yes.
That Lil Jon era, that was a time.
Like 05 to 07.
When you could just play like all those records back to back.
And it literally was, from the window.
Yeah.
I was like, it was a time.
It was a time.
We are, we are, we are.